Port of Yokohama - Japan
Overload..
How did the red sandalwood come here without being informed?
Call the boss now.
Hello boss, there's a Container full of red sandalwood here in our port
Okey boss!
Did you know who sent those things?
I don't know sir..
See the name of the
shipping company.
BASHBV, Boss
- BASHBV?
- Yes, boss.  BASHBV.
Sir..there is a man inside,
It looks like he's still alive.
He looks like an Indian.
But how is he?
42 days in a row without
food or water in that container?
Are you still in Panapit?
Go and find out boys..
Hang him upside down.
Who are you and..
Who sent these items?
Bring someone to interrogate
him who can speak his language.
Bring him fast
Hello boss..
He is from India.
Find out what is his name..how
did he get into this.
Ask, for whom he
has brought this goods.
All right, boss. I will ask
[Tamil] Oi who are you..Telugu or Tamil?
He asks who
brought those things..
He did not give an answer
Which means he's a Telugu, Sir
I didn't ask that.
Oi..why don't you talk?
Who are you?
Pushpa..
Kill him...
Get your weapons ready!
Kill him
English resync and encoded by @aryiff
[Japanese] Hello!
My Japanese brothers..
How are you?
I have been thinking for a long time, what
is the country like, to which we send goods,
I finally saw it today.
How?
This country is very cold.
Very cold! Cold!
Japanese...
Hey what's this..can
you speak Japanese?
42 days in the container
just wondering why
Learned Japanese in 42 days
How is my Japanese...
[Japanese] Awesome! Great!
So, what is your reason
for coming to Japan?
When the goods
arrived in Japan..
No money came to Tirupati.
I'm here to show you, What
happens if you mess with the Indians?
...
With the blessings of
Sri Mulleti Parvathiamma..
Your mother's name is printed
on the letter of invitation, please
Look at this..look at this..
Sons and daughter-in-law..
Shri Mulleti
Pushparaj..Mrs. Shri Valli..
All the names were noted
down.. I forgot one name, please
Name of Sri Mulleti Chinna
(Podi) Venkataramanan..
Please...
What is this?
don't cry please
Pushpa..
what happened
daughter?.. Pushpa..
- Is my mother-in-law okay?
- I'm fine.
come on
little uncle
Can you call me ``aunt'' now?
All came..but
Where is the person
who really wants to come?
Didn't he come?
He didn't come
sir..sent a message.
what happened
what happened sister in law
The little one is
dancing with happiness..
Son..
Now everyone is there,
Don't move at all..
English resync and encoded by @aryiff
Coming Soon! Pushpa 3 - The
Rampage (Deception)